

### PROFILE

I am a driven data engineer and robotics developer. Programming and working with computers in general has been a passion for quite some time.

In love with automation and minimizing repetitive work, which is why I'm able to focus on efficient & application-oriented learning, developing and problem solving.

Switching views, working on agile projects and changing approaches often motivate me to study new topics, tackle hard challenges and deliver results.

**BIRTHDATE** 

11 januari 2000

**ADDRESS** 

Houthalen-Helchteren, Belgium

PHONE NUMBER

+32486539354

MAILING ADDRESS

kobethuwis26@gmail.com

GITHUB PORTFOLIO LINKEDIN

# KOBE THUWIS

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

InfoFarm: Data Consultant 2021 - Present

# Lineas Data Squad

Lineas is the largest private rail freight operator in Europe. I develop and setup Kubernetes clusters, AWS data pools and NiFi data flows using Terraform and custom scripts, in order to provide a central data storage and management platform.

# ANPR Big Data Platform

The ANPR Big Data Platform is a scalable and extensible platform for collecting, storing and aggregating ANPR data. My task within the project is to construct a big data lake using AWS and make the data usable for analysis, reporting and future processing.

### PXL Smart ICT: Research & Development Intern 2021

ArtiFISHal Intelligence is a twofold project, primarily consisting of scenes made in Unity which illustrate several reinforcement learning techniques. Secondly, the project contains a simulation of a marine ecosystem which uses an open-ended algorithm, NEAT.

Chiro Meulenberg: Head Monitor 2018 - Present

Strandbal: Event Manager 2018 - Present

Youth Council Member 2019 - Present

### **EDUCATION**

**Amazon Web Services** 2021 - Present AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

**Hogeschool PXL** 2018 - 2021 Bachelor Applied Information Technology (Al & Robotics)

**Kindsheid Jesu** 2012 - 2018 High school diploma in Maths & Sciences